showyou.com 2012-12-22

# Showyou: Watch videos from your friends

This Privacy Policy describes what information we collect from you and how we use it (or, in some cases, intend to use it). 

Showyou receives your information when you sign up for and create an account on one of our iOS apps (iPad, iPhone, or iPod Touch) or our Kindle Fire app, as well as when you use our application. For example, you send us information when you use Showyou to share videos, watch videos, or comment on videos. 

By voluntarily using Showyou and creating an account with your service, you consent to the various uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at feedback@showyou.com. 

## Information Collection and Use

**Why We Collect Information from You:** We collect the information set out below for two main reasons: (1) to make the Showyou application work for you as designed, primarily by bringing in videos shared by your friends and other contacts on social networks you use and making it easy to share videos you like on those social networks; and (2) to enable us to make money, primarily by making sure the advertisements distributed through Showyou are properly targeted, and best match your tastes and interests. 

**Information Collected Upon Registration:** When you create a Showyou account, or connect Showyou to outside services like Facebook, Twitter, or YouTube, you provide some personal information that helps us to make the Showyou application instantly responsive and customized to your tastes by bringing in videos from the social networks and video sites you use. 

Facebook  
If you register with Facebook, or later connect Showyou to Facebook, we ask and Facebook provides us with the following information which we store on our servers: your user ID; the link to your profile URL on Facebook; your thumbnail image and your name; any “about me” biography” you’ve entered on Facebook; your interests; and your location and birthday. Facebook also provides us with your access credentials and and “offline access” to your Facebook account so that we can find videos shared by your friends in your Facebook feed, and so that we can publish videos to your Facebook profile on your behalf when you share a video out to Facebook. 

Twitter  
If you register with Twitter, or later connect Showyou to Twitter, we ask and Twitter provides us with the following information which we store on our servers: your Twitter Id; your screen name and profile image; and your access credentials so we can post Tweets on your behalf and bring in videos shared by people you follow from your Twitter feed. 

YouTube  
If you connect Showyou to YouTube, we ask and YouTube provides us with access credentials that enable us to retrieve videos shared by people and organizations you follow (or are “subscribed to”) on YouTube. 

Vimeo  
If you connect Showyou to Vimeo, we ask and YouTube provides us with access credentials that enable us to retrieve videos shared by people and organizations you follow (or are “subscribed to”) on Vimeo. 

Tumblr  
If you connect Showyou to Tumblr, we ask you for and store your username and password to enable us to retrieve videos shared by people and organizations you follow (or are “subscribed to”) on Tumblr. 

**Information from Your Address Book and Social Networks Used for Friend Finder:** When you register and create an account from the iPhone or iPad, you may opt-in to use the email addresses in your Address Book to determine if you have contacts already on Showyou, in order to help you connect with those contacts. We do not store any of this data. 

If you have signed up using Facebook or Twitter, or connected Showyou to those services after signup, we also look up your contacts from those services to determine if friends or people you follow are already on Showyou. We do not store any of this data. 

**Videos from Your Social Networks:** Once you’ve connected Showyou to these accounts, we bring in videos shared by your contacts on these services (i.e., by your friends on Facebook, or people you follow on Twitter) along with related comments or tweets, enabling you to see all of the videos shared on these social networks in one place. We store specific information about these videos in order to make them accessible to you via the Showyou app, and information in aggregate about these videos in order to make them accessible through Showyou search, our popular list. 

When you share a video via one of the services you’ve connected to Showyou (for example, through a public tweet or public post on Facebook, or favorite a video on YouTube) it will be shared on your Showyou grid, and displayed to people who follow you on Showyou or who visit your Showyou grid. 

**Email Address and Additional Information:** During registration, we ask for an email address. You may also provide us with additional information to make public, such as a short biography or a picture. We may use your contact information to send you information about our Services or to market to you. You can unsubscribe from these messages by following the instructions contained within the messages or the instructions on our web site. If you email us, we may keep your message, email address and contact information to respond to your request. 

**Commenting On and Sharing Videos:** When you use the Showyou app, you may interact with videos by sharing them on Showyou, commenting on them, or sharing them by email or to Twitter of Facebook. When you share a video within Showyou, or comment on a video, we store that information in order to display your comment publicly to other users on Showyou and to share the video on your Showyou grid. 

**Log Data:** Our servers automatically record information ("Log Data") when you use the Showyou app. This Log Data may include information such as your IP address, device and application IDs, videos you watch or mark to watch later, and search terms. Other actions, such as interactions with our apps, website, and advertisements, may also be included in Log Data. If we haven’t already deleted the Log Data earlier, we will either delete it or remove any common account identifiers, such as your username, full IP address, or email address, after 18 months. 

**Cookies:** Like many websites, we use "cookie" technology to collect additional website usage data and to improve our Services. A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to your computer's hard disk. Showyou may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with our Services, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on our Services, and to improve our Services. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. 

**Third Party Services:** Showyou uses services hosted by third parties to help us understand the use of our application, such as Google Analytics. These services may collect information sent by our applications or your browser in order to provide us with analytics and measurement services. 

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

**Your Consent:** We may share or disclose your information with your consent, such as when you use a third party web client or application to access your Showyou account. 

**Service Providers:** We may engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us. We may share your personal information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services, and only pursuant to obligations mirroring the protections of this privacy policy. 

**Law and Harm:** We may preserve or disclose your information if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect Showyou's rights or property. 

**Business Transfers:** In the event that Showyou is involved in a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, your information may be sold or transferred as part of that transaction. The promises in this privacy policy will apply to your information as transferred to the new entity. 

**Non-Private or Non-Personal Information:** We may share or disclose your non-private, aggregated or otherwise non-personal information, such as your public Tweets or the number of users who clicked on a particular link (even if only one did). Changes to this Policy 

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the policy will govern our use of your information and will always be at http://showyou.com/privacy. If we make a change to this policy that, in our sole discretion, is material, we will notify you via e-mail to the email associated with your account. By continuing to access or use the Services after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy. 

Effective: March 1, 2012
